Guide to the Sarah Thomas papers,1996-2006.
Thomas, Sarah papers,1996-2006.
- Zimelman, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Sarah's Chron File, 2002- (Box 19, Folder 20-29)
  10 folders
- Sarah's Chron File, 2002- (Box 20, Folder 1-4)
  4 folders; also see box 7 folder 29 General Correspondence- Sarah Thomas (2006)
- Math Conference, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- CLIR, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 6-22)
  17 folders
- Workforce Planning, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 23-33)
- Workforce Planning, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 1-26)
  26 folders
- HED/HEGIS, 1993- (Box 22, Folder 1-34)
  34 folders
- Sarah's Chron File, 2002- (Box 23, Folder 1-19)
  19 folders